tfsource.com 2017-06-06

# TF Source Privacy Policy

Shop all sites, use one cart!

$150.00 until **FREE SHIPPING!**

### What information do you collect?

We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way, including site registration, order placements, newsletter subscriptions and survey responses.

Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You can opt out of providing certain information and visit our site anonymously. However, you may not be able to take advantage of many of our features.

### What do you use my information for?

We use information you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our site and communicating with you.

### Order Fulfillment

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.

### Personalized Emails

The email address you provide for order processing is used only to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request.

### How do you protect my information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information whenyou submit a request, place an order or access your personal information. 

These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information, SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. All sensitive credit card information is stored on our third-party processors site. TFS does not store any credit card information on our site.

### What if someone gets unauthorized access to my account?

It’s important for you to prevent unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

#### Do you use cookies?

No, we do not use cookies.

### Do you use third-party service providers?

Yes, we use trusted third-party service providers who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but may not use it for other purposes. With the exception of these trusted third-party service providers, we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties. 

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### Is TFS compliant with online privacy acts?

Yes. Please see below.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ' **Edit Profile**' page.

### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

In compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

### CAN-SPAM Compliance

We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

### Terms & Conditions

Please also visit our Terms & Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [**tfsource.com**](https://tfsource.com/).

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on  **6` / ` 25 ` / ` 2011**. 

### What if I have questions about the Privacy Policy?

If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy you may contact us using the information below.  
[ **tfsource.com**](https://tfsource.com/).  
508 SW 15th Ave, Suite C  
Lake Forest, MN 55025 USA  
651-464-6961

### Privacy Policy Customer Pledge

We pledge to you, our customer, that we have made a dedicated effort to bring our Privacy Policy in line with the following important privacy laws and initiatives:

  * Federal Trade Commission Fair
  * California Online Privacy Protection Act
  * Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act
  * Privacy Alliance
  * Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act

If at anytime you have a cause that needs to be disputed, please fill out the Trust Guard Dispute Resolution form.

Sincerely,

 **Curt, Jerry the Dino & the TFS Team**
